So far in this lesson we've talked about how we can show disagreement with others either in a very polite
到目前为止，在本课中，我们已经讨论了如何以非常礼貌的方式表达与他人的分歧
way or a more direct way.
方式或更直接的方式。
And how when we have disagreements we can come to a compromise.
当我们有分歧时，我们如何达成妥协。
For example in a negotiation or when we need to bargain and how we can use phrases to express that we're
例如在谈判中或当我们需要讨价还价时，以及我们如何使用短语来表达我们是
ready to give something up.
准备放弃一些东西。
Now we're going to talk about another type of difficult situation a difficult choice and you have to
现在我们要讨论另一种困难的情况，一个艰难的选择，你必须
make a choice.
取舍。
That's not fun.
这不好玩。
There are two really common expressions and I want to teach you the two expressions because they are
有两种非常常见的表达方式，我想教你这两种表达方式，因为它们是
very common and very useful.
很常见也很有用。
And then we're going to actually look at some examples.
然后我们将实际看一些例子。
One of them could be a choice between two good things but it's difficult still.
其中之一可能是两件好事之间的选择，但这仍然很困难。
Right.
正确的。
But the two choices are good positive.
但是这两个选择是好的积极的。
The other is definitely for bad things definitely for negative things.
另一个绝对是针对坏事的，绝对是针对消极的事。
So let's learn these two and then look at the examples.
所以让我们学习这两个，然后看例子。
Have you ever been in a situation where you have two choices.
你有没有遇到过两种选择的情况。
There's just so hard to make one or the other.
很难做到其中一个。
It may be that it's because this choice is not great in this choice is not great but it may often be
可能是因为这个选择不是很好在这个选择不是很好但它可能经常是
because this choice is very good very attractive and this choice is very good very attractive choice
因为这个选择非常好非常有吸引力而且这个选择非常好非常有吸引力的选择
and choice B are both great choices.
和选项B都是不错的选择。
You don't know which one to go with which means choose to go with.
你不知道该选择哪一个，这意味着选择和。
OK so on the fence is the expression I'm on the fence I'm on the fence.
好的，所以在栅栏上是我在栅栏上的表达我在栅栏上。
Well what what does that mean.
那是什么意思。
Let's break that down.
让我们分解一下。
Well a fence is something that divides two things.
好吧，栅栏是将两件事分开的东西。
For example there's a home here with a yard and a home here with a yard.
例如这里有一个带院子的家，这里有一个带院子的家。
Let me draw a very fast and very ugly home.
让我画一个非常快而且非常丑陋的家。
There's a home here a tree and a yard and.
这里有一个家，一棵树和一个院子。
OK.
好的。
And there's a home here and then the little tree.
这里有一个家，然后是那棵小树。
This one's bigger.
这个比较大
Oh this bigger tree and a yard.
哦，这棵更大的树和一个院子。
OK so two houses now in the middle.
好的，所以现在中间有两个房子。
In the middle there's a fence.
中间有栅栏。
There's a fence here and it divides the two properties one property two properties.
这里有一个栅栏，它把两个属性一个属性两个属性分开。
Now you can imagine walking on the fence right.
现在你可以想象走在栅栏上吧。
If you're walking on the fence it takes great balance.
如果您在栅栏上行走，则需要很好的平衡。
We use this visual idea this visual idea to communicate that we don't know if we should fall off on
我们用这个视觉想法这个视觉想法来传达我们不知道我们是否应该放弃
this side or fall off on this side.
这一面或从这一面脱落。
We don't know.
我们不知道。
That's why we're on the fence about whether to A or B whether to go with A or B.
这就是为什么我们在选择 A 还是 B 是否选择 A 或 B 的问题上犹豫不决。
I'm really on the fence about whether whether often I should do A or go with B.
我真的在犹豫是否应该经常做A还是和B一起去。
I just don't know.
我只是不知道。
So let's look at an example we talked about the two houses.
因此，让我们看一个我们谈到两所房子的例子。
So we should have a pretty good idea about what on the fence means.
所以我们应该对栅栏上的含义有一个很好的了解。
Let's actually look at a case where we can use it.
让我们实际看一个我们可以使用它的案例。
OK.
好的。
I got offers from both talking about two two companies here.
我从这里得到了两家公司的报价。
If you go to a job interview you apply to a company and you go to an interview and you do well maybe
如果你去面试，你申请了一家公司，你去面试，你可能做得很好
you do that at two different companies and you get an offer that means they would like you to work for
你在两家不同的公司做这件事，你得到了一份工作，这意味着他们希望你为之工作
them.
他们。
So that's a good thing.
所以这是一件好事。
I got offers from both and I'm completely on the fence about which one to choose.
我得到了两者的报价，我完全不知道该选择哪一个。
We could also remember say about whether to choose that or x box game company X Box offers great benefits
我们还记得说是选择那个还是 X Box 游戏公司 X Box 提供了很大的好处
a great benefits package benefits are the extra things besides your salary basic things your salary
一个很好的福利包福利是除了你的薪水之外的额外的东西你的薪水基本的东西你的薪水是的
your salary benefits are things like health insurance.
你的工资福利就像健康保险。
And sometimes sometimes we have an expense account which means you can have a credit card and you just
有时我们有一个费用账户，这意味着您可以拥有一张信用卡，而您只需
swipe it when you buy stuff an expense account anyway x box offers a great benefits package and the
买东西的时候刷一下 总之费用账户 x box 提供了一个很好的福利包和
pay is fantastic.
薪水太棒了。
That means the salary is fantastic.
这意味着薪水很棒。
Those are two different things.
这是两个不同的东西。
But Apple seems to have better long term prospects prospects in terms of promotions.
但就促销而言，苹果似乎有更好的长期前景前景。
I could really go either way at this point and I could use some help.
在这一点上，我真的可以去任何一种方式，我可以使用一些帮助。
So we would maybe give advice to this person.
所以我们也许会给这个人一些建议。
Oh you poor you poor you.
哦，你可怜你可怜你。
You have the choice to work at two very good companies with a great salary and you can't choose.
你可以选择在两家非常好的公司工作，薪水很高，你无法选择。
Oh no I say follow your heart or go and live in a cave.
哦不，我说跟随你的心或去住在山洞里。
OK.
好的。
So here when we say in terms of promotions that means chances to get a better job in the future better
所以在这里，当我们说升职时，这意味着将来有机会更好地获得更好的工作
prospects means you have some good possibilities in the future.
前景意味着你在未来有一些很好的可能性。
If you're standing on a hill and you look out over the horizon your prospects are the things that are
如果你站在一座小山上，你眺望地平线，你的前景就是眼前的事物
possible for you have no prospects.
可能因为你没有前景。
It could be for your relationships could be for your career often for a career.
可能是为了你的人际关系，也可能是为了你的事业，通常是为了事业。
So here's how we use on the fence.
所以这就是我们如何在栅栏上使用。
And usually it's for two good things.
通常是为了两件好事。
But again not always.
但同样并非总是如此。
Now let's look at another expression which is very similar and can also express a difficult choice but
现在让我们看另一个非常相似的表达方式，也可以表达一个困难的选择，但是
it is for two negative things.
这是为了两件消极的事情。
The next expression for describing a difficult choice where both choices are bad is between a rock and
描述两个选择都不好的困难选择的下一个表达是在岩石和
a hard place.
一个艰难的地方。
Now this has a very interesting physical sort of visual description connected to it which helps us really
现在这有一个非常有趣的物理类型的视觉描述与之相关，这对我们真的很有帮助
understand it.
明白它。
There is a movie called One Hundred and twenty seven hours and it's about a man who goes hiking in.
有一部电影叫一百二十七小时，讲的是一个人去远足。
He ends up in a canyon.
他最终进入了一个峡谷。
The rock wall came and there's a boulder which is a big stones Canyon is to two stone walls on both
石墙来了，那里有一块巨石，它是一块大石头，峡谷是两个石墙
sides of you.
你的侧面。
We could also call it a crevice if it's smaller so maybe it's a crevice whatever and a Boulder is a
如果它更小，我们也可以称它为裂缝，所以也许它是一个裂缝，而 Boulder 是一个
big stone.
大石头。
OK.
好的。
And he gets his hand stuck between the rock and the wall and he can't get it out and he's there for
他的手被卡在岩石和墙壁之间，他不能把它弄出来，他在那里等着
days.
天。
This is a true story.
这是一个真实的故事。
The movie is not the real thing but the story is real.
电影不是真实的，但故事是真实的。
And he has to make a choice should I stay here and die.
他必须做出选择，让我留在这里等死。
That's choice.
那是选择。
A one choice a stay here and die from starvation or lack of water.
一个选择留在这里，死于饥饿或缺水。
Choice B choice number two also not good.
选项 B 选项二也不好。
Cut my hand off.
砍掉我的手。
I have a very old not very sharp knife.
我有一把很旧也不是很锋利的刀。
I would have to break the bone and cut my arm off because that's what stuck between the the wall and
我将不得不折断骨头并切断我的手臂，因为那是卡在墙壁和
the the Boulder.
博尔德。
So there are two choices.
所以有两种选择。
Both choices are terrible.
这两种选择都很糟糕。
So we say I'm between a rock and a hard place.
所以我们说我在一块石头和一个坚硬的地方之间。
The interesting thing about this one is that he's actually between a rock this thing which is a rock
关于这个的有趣之处在于，他实际上是在一块岩石之间，这东西是一块岩石
and a hard place the wall.
和一个坚硬的地方墙壁。
So it's very physically meaningful to you can picture it very clearly I think.
所以它对你来说非常有意义，我认为它可以非常清晰地描绘出来。
Don't picture it too clearly.
不要画得太清楚。
He ended up cutting his arm off by the way.
最后他顺便砍断了他的手臂。
He survived but he had to cut his arm off very slowly.
他活了下来，但他不得不非常缓慢地切断他的手臂。
No fun.
没有什么好玩的。
So we used this expression when we're in any kind of situation like this.
因此，当我们处于这样的任何情况下时，我们都会使用这个表达方式。
Two difficult choices to make.
两个艰难的选择制作。
We don't know which one to choose.
我们不知道该选择哪一个。
It's not fun.
这不好玩。
So let's look at an example.
所以让我们看一个例子。
This example comes from a business owner someone who's owning a business and it's a small business.
这个例子来自一个企业主，他拥有一家企业，它是一家小企业。
It's a shop to shop maybe a bookshop a coffee shop and it's not doing well.
这是一家商店，也许是一家书店，一家咖啡店，但做得并不好。
It's not doing very well not making very much money.
赚的钱不是很多，做的不是很好。
Maybe customers aren't coming in for some reason.
也许客户出于某种原因没有进来。
So the shop owner says if things aren't looking good either way either way means it could be that way
所以店主说，如果事情看起来不太好，任何一种方式都意味着它可能是那样的
or that way.
或者那样。
Both options are bad.
两种选择都很糟糕。
You could go either way means you could go this way.
你可以走任何一种方式意味着你可以走这条路。
Go left go right.
向左向右。
Things aren't looking good either way.
事情看起来都不怎么好。
I could either close my shop and file for bankruptcy.
我可以关闭我的商店并申请破产。
Bankruptcy is when you basically announce formally legally that you cannot pay back money that you've
破产是当你基本上合法地正式宣布你不能偿还你已经支付的钱
borrowed.
借来的。
And it's sort of like a restart on your financial situation file for bankruptcy or borrow more money
这有点像重新启动您的财务状况申请破产或借更多钱
and try to breathe new life into the business.
并尝试为业务注入新的活力。
This is another expression to breathe life into something is to to try to give it a fresh start or something
这是给某物注入生命的另一种表达方式是尝试给它一个新的开始或某事
new something fresh so that it can change.
新的东西，以便它可以改变。
While that change in my diet really breathed new life into my daily routine I have much more energy
虽然我的饮食改变确实为我的日常生活注入了新的活力，但我有更多的精力
now be a simple example.
现在做一个简单的例子。
I guess you could say I'm between a rock and a hard place.
我想你可以说我在一块石头和一个坚硬的地方之间。
Or you could say I'm really between a rock and a hard place.
或者你可以说我真的是介于两难之间。
Or you could just directly say I'm between a rock and a hard place.
或者你可以直接说我在一块石头和一个坚硬的地方之间。
So this one doesn't fit very well within the description of what the two bad choices are.
所以这个不太适合描述两个糟糕的选择是什么。
It's usually a sentence by itself unlike the other one.
它通常是一个句子，与另一个句子不同。
I'm on the fence because we say I'm on the fence about whether to a or b but this one.
我犹豫不决，因为我们说我对是否选择 a 或 b 持谨慎态度，但这个。
We say I'm between a rock and a hard place.
我们说我在一块石头和一个坚硬的地方之间。
I'm really between a rock and a hard place either at the beginning or the end of the description of
无论是在描述的开头还是结尾，我真的是介于两者之间
what the two things are.
这两件事是什么。
So it's used differently.
所以使用方式不同。
It's usually separated from the actual description.
它通常与实际描述分开。
So when we want to actually recommend what our friend should do in either situation either the on the
因此，当我们想要真正推荐我们的朋友在任何一种情况下应该做什么时
fence situation with the two companies or the company that's about to go bankrupt unless the owner borrows
除非所有者借款，否则与两家公司或即将破产的公司保持隔离
more money.
更多钱。
How do we give advice to these people.
我们如何给这些人提供建议。
Well we can use the phrase best bet best bet as a way to say this is what I think would be the smartest
好吧，我们可以使用短语 best be best bet 来表达我认为这是最聪明的
choice it is most likely it is most likely the best choice when we're giving our opinion about something
当我们对某事发表意见时，它很可能是最好的选择
we might be talking about the probability of success or how likely it is that this idea is going to
我们可能会谈论成功的可能性或这个想法的可能性有多大
be the one that you should choose the one that works out in the long run.
成为您应该选择从长远来看可以解决的问题。
Finally basically is the meaning.
最后基本上就是这个意思了。
OK so best bet your best bet is to your best bet is to let's look at the examples for the first situation.
好的，所以最好的选择是最好的选择是让我们看一下第一种情况的示例。
Your best bet would be to go with the company that has better long term prospects long term means not
你最好的选择是选择具有更好长期前景的公司长期意味着不
not just now not just money now but in the far future go with.
不只是现在不只是现在的钱，而是在遥远的未来。
Remember go with means choose the company that has better long term prospects.
记住选择意味着选择具有更好长期前景的公司。
And again basically it means that's what I think is the smartest choice the most likely to be successful
基本上，这意味着我认为这是最明智的选择，最有可能成功
to be good for you in the long run.
从长远来看对你有好处。
In the second situation number two your best bet might be to hire a marketing team and try to revive
在第二种情况下，您最好的选择可能是聘请营销团队并尝试复兴
the business revive means to bring it back to life it's almost dead to come back to life.
商业复兴意味着让它起死回生，起死回生几乎是死路一条。
Come back to life.
回来生活。
Revive the business.
重振事业。
If you give up now you may never get another shot at it.
如果你现在放弃，你可能再也没有机会尝试它了。
This shot is another try another attempt another try another attempt at it.
这个镜头是另一个尝试另一个尝试另一个尝试另一个尝试。
This may be your only chance to follow your dream of having a bookstore so your best bet.
这可能是您实现拥有一家书店的梦想的唯一机会，因此您是最好的选择。
The smartest thing for you to do the thing that's most likely to lead to success for you is to hire
做最有可能为你带来成功的事情对你来说最聪明的事情就是雇佣
a marketing team.
营销团队。
In this lesson we've learned quite a few new phrases for describing difficult situations and describing
在这一课中，我们学习了很多新的短语来描述困难的情况和描述
disagreement as well as compromise.
分歧和妥协。
So what I'd like you to do is try to describe a situation in which you've had to make a difficult choice
所以我想让你做的是试着描述一个你不得不做出艰难选择的情况
a difficult choice.
一个艰难的选择。
Try to describe both the pros the good things and the cons of both choices of the choices.
尝试描述这两种选择的优点和缺点。
Record yourself so speak into your phone and then listen to it again.
录制自己，然后对着手机说话，然后再听一遍。
Make sure to use the expressions from this lesson and write down any mistakes you find so that you can
确保使用本课中的表达方式并写下您发现的任何错误，以便您可以
become more aware of those mistakes so that you can hear them when you're seeing them next time.
更加意识到这些错误，以便下次看到它们时可以听到它们。
Good luck.
祝你好运。